(Sheldon:)Amy, please. I am trying
to figure out a way
(Sheldon:)to intellectually emasculate
a dear friend of mine.
(Amy:)But I'm just...
Not now.
(Amy:)You better watch
that attitude, buddy.
(Amy:)You're dating the
popular girl now.
(Leonard:)Hmm. You're up late.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm working on
my lesson plan for Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)He is going to be so lost.
(Sheldon:)Look at this section over here.
(Sheldon:)Even I don't really
understand it.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, why are you doing this?
(Sheldon:)I'm a teacher, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)It's my job.
No, I-I mean,
(Leonard:)why are you going
to so much trouble
(Leonard:)to prove that you're smarter
than Wolowitz?
Oh, it's no trouble;
it's actually a pleasure.
(Leonard:)You want to know what I think?
(Leonard:)I think the idea that someone
could be as smart as you,
(Leonard:)or even smarter,
scares the pants off you,
(Leonard:)and you can't deal with it.
(Sheldon:)Interesting point.